promgirl.net 2016-05-09

# Privacy Policy | Promgirl.net

Promgirl Inc. Privacy Policy

Here at Promgirl Inc. we are committed to protecting the privacy of our customers. The below privacy policy details how Promgirl Inc. collects and uses any personal information that you provide on our website: Promgirl.net. It also explains the choices available to you regarding Promgirl Inc.’s use of your personal information and the steps that you can take to access, review and request corrections of this information. 

Promgirl.net is hosted by Yahoo! Store. Yahoo! hosts all store pages as well as the ordering system and all order data. Yahoo! automatically collects all order information but is only permitted to use such information in the aggregate. If you accessed this store directly through Yahoo! Shopping then Yahoo! also automatically collects information regarding your shopping experience. Please see the Yahoo! Privacy Policy for more details on how Yahoo! uses the information it collects. 

Promgirl Inc. has been awarded the Norton Secured Seal by VeriSign which signifies that the below Privacy Policy and practices describe therein have been reviewed by VeriSign and found in compliance with all the VeriSign Program requirements including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. VeriSign’s mission, as an independent third party organization is to provide and check online security and trust among consumers and business organizations on a global scale.

Collection and Use of Personal Information

Orders

If you purchase a product from us we will request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. Required information includes both personal contact information such as name, email address and shipping address as well as financial information such as credit card number and expiration date. This information is used for billing purposes and to ensure that your order is filled correctly. In the event that we have trouble processing an order we will also use this information to contact you regarding whatever issue is prohibiting the completion of the order. All credit card information is stored in the secured Yahoo! servers for a period of three (3) weeks. After the three (3) week period has expired all pertinent information related to credit card transactions is automatically erased from the servers for security purposes.

Third-Party Web Beacons

We use third-party web beacons from Yahoo to help analyze where visitors go and what they do while visiting our website. Yahoo may also use anonymous information about your visits to this and other websites in order to improve its products and services and provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by Yahoo, [click here](http://info.yahoo.com/privacy/us/yahoo/opt_out/targeting/details.html). 

Customer Service

Once you have placed an order on our site we will send you an email to confirm your purchase. We may also communicate with you in response to any inquires you may have, to provide specific services you might request and to help manage your account. We will communicate with you by either email or telephone depending on and in accordance with your wishes.

Tell-A-Friend

If you choose to make use of our referral service in order to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s email address in order to send a one-time emailing inviting your friend to visit our site. Promgirl Inc. does not have access to this information (see: “Links to Other Sites” section below for more detailed information). Reviews and Testimonials Should you choose to post a review on this site please be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit therein may be read, collected or used by other users viewing these forums. We post testimonials and reviews as well as comments received from our customers via email to help new users better understand our commitment to customer service and providing quality products. Promgirl Inc. is not responsible for any personally identifiable information that you choose to submit in these forums. 

Disclosure and Information Sharing

Promgirl Inc. will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described within this privacy policy. We do not sell, rent or otherwise trade your personal information with third parties unless specifically described in this privacy policy. 

Agents and Service Providers

Promgirl Inc. uses outside shipping companies to fulfill orders, these companies are UPS and USPS. We also use a credit card processing company to bill you for shipping goods and shipping services. In addition to these companies we also work with a fraud verification service to help us verify the validity of all credit cards used on our site and prevent identity theft. The companies described herein do not retain, share, store or use the personally identifiable information you have provided to Promgirl.net for any purposes other than those described in this paragraph.

Legal Disclaimer

Promgirl Inc. reserves the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that such disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or any legal process served on our website. 

Log Files

As with most websites we automatically gather certain information from any user who views our site and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, internet service provider (ISP), browser type, referring and exit pages, operating system, date and time stamp, and click-stream data. This information does not identify individual users and is only used to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movement around the site and gather general demographic information about our user base. We do not at any time link this automatically collected and logged data to any personally indefinable information. 

Cookies

Cookies are small text files that are stored on a user’s computer for record keeping purposes. This site utilizes cookies. We do not link the information stored in cookies to any personally identifiable information you may submit while on our site. If you reject the use of cookies you may still use our site however your ability to use specific areas of Promgirl.net may be limited for this reason. Promgirl Inc. uses third party tracking services that utilize cookies as well as tracking technologies that track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site in the aggregate for the purpose of tracking usage and volume statistics. Some of our business partners, such as advertisers, also use cookies and tracking technologies on our site. We have no access to these cookies and no control over them. This privacy policy covers the use of cookies by Promgirl.net only and does not cover the use of cookies by any third parties mentioned herein. 

Clear GIFs

Some of our third party advertising partners employ a software technology called clear GIFs, also known as Web Beacons or Web Bugs, that help us better manage content on our site by informing us as to which content is most effective. Clear GIFs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies which are used to track the online movements of web users. In contract to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear GIFs are embedded invisibly on web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not at any time link the information gathered by Clear GIFs to any personally indefinable information.

Advertising

We partner with a third party advertising network to display advertising on our site and to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner uses cookies and well as clear GIFs to collection non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other websites to provide you with targeted advertising based on your interests.

Links to Other Sites

Promgirl.net contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Promgirl Inc. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage all users to be aware of this and advise that when you leave our site you read the privacy policies of each and every website that collections personally identifiable information as this privacy policy only applies to information collected by our website, Promgirl.net.

Security The security of your personal information is very important to use. Whenever you enter sensitive information such as credit card numbers on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer (SSL) technology. As a Yahoo! store Promgirl.net employs the highest standards of internet security measures designed to protect the consumer, both during the transmission of sensitive data and once we receive it. However no method of transmission over the internet or method of electronic storage is proven to be 100% secure. Therefore while we strive to use the best commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions regarding security on our website please email us at info@promgirl.net

Access to Personally Identifiable Information

If your personally identifiable information changes, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by sending an email directed to Customer Support Staff to info@promgirl.net or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail using the contact information listed below.

Changes in the Privacy Policy

If at any point Promgirl Inc. decides to change or amend our privacy policy those changes will be posted to this privacy policy as well as other locations we deem appropriate for making our users aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

Promgirl Inc. reserves the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this privacy policy, we will notify our users here, by email or by another means of notification posted on our home page.
